[
    {
        "question": "What is the name for the Jewish New Year?",
        "answers": [
            "Hanukkah",
            "Yom Kippur",
            "Kwanza",
            "Rosh Hashanah"
        ],
        "answer": "Rosh Hashanah"
    },
    {
        "question": " How many blue stripes are there on the U.S. flag?",
        "answers": [
            "6",
            "7",
            "13",
            "0"
        ],
        "answer": "0"
    },
    {
        "question": " Which one of these characters is not friends with Harry Potter?",
        "answers": [
            "Ron Weasley",
            "Neville Longbottom",
            "Draco Malfoy",
            "Hermione Granger"
        ],
        "answer": "Draco Malfoy"
    },
    {
        "question": " What is the color of Donald Duck\u2019s bowtie?",
        "answers": [
            "Red",
            "Yellow",
            "Blue",
            "White"
        ],
        "answer": "Red"
    },
    {
        "question": " What was the name of the band Lionel Richie was a part of?",
        "answers": [
            "King Harvest",
            "Spectrums",
            "Commodores",
            "The Marshall Tucker Band"
        ],
        "answer": "Commodores"
    },
    {
        "question": " Which animal does not appear in the Chinese zodiac?",
        "answers": [
            "Dragon",
            "Rabbit",
            "Dog",
            "Hummingbird"
        ],
        "answer": "Hummingbird"
    },
    {
        "question": " Which country held the 2016 Summer Olympics?",
        "answers": [
            "China",
            "Ireland",
            "Brazil",
            "Italy"
        ],
        "answer": "Brazil"
    },
    {
        "question": " Which planet is the hottest?",
        "answers": [
            "Venus",
            "Saturn",
            "Mercury",
            "Mars"
        ],
        "answer": "Venus"
    },
    {
        "question": " Who was the only U.S. President to resign?",
        "answers": [
            "Herbert Hoover",
            "Richard Nixon",
            "George W. Bush",
            "Barack Obama"
        ],
        "answer": "Nixon"
    },
    {
        "question": " What does the \u201cD\u201d in \u201cD-Day\u201d stand for?",
        "answers": [
            "Dooms",
            "Dark",
            "Day ",
            "Dunkirk"
        ],
        "answer": "Day"
    },
    {
        "question": " In which city can you find the Liberty Bell?",
        "answers": [
            "Washington, D.C.",
            "Boston",
            "Philadelphia",
            "Manhattan "
        ],
        "answer": "Philadelphia"
    },
    {
        "question": " In Pirates of the Caribbean, what was Captain Jack Sparrow\u2019s ship\u2019s name?",
        "answers": [
            "The Marauder",
            "The Black Pearl",
            "The Black Python",
            "The Slytherin"
        ],
        "answer": "The Black Pearl"
    },
    {
        "question": " According to Forrest Gump, \u201clife was like\u2026\u201d",
        "answers": [
            "A bag of lemons",
            "A handful of roses",
            "A lollipop",
            "A box of chocolates"
        ],
        "answer": "A box of chocolates"
    },
    {
        "question": " Linda and Bob from Bob\u2019s Burgers have 3 kids. Which one of these characters is not one of them?",
        "answers": [
            "Louise",
            "Gene",
            "Jimmy",
            "Tina"
        ],
        "answer": "Jimmy"
    },
    {
        "question": " The British band One Direction (rip) was made up of Harry, Louis, Niall, Zayn, and\u2026",
        "answers": [
            "Paul",
            "Callum",
            "Kevin",
            "Liam"
        ],
        "answer": "Liam"
    },
    {
        "question": " What is the rarest blood type?",
        "answers": [
            "O",
            "A",
            "B",
            "AB-Negative"
        ],
        "answer": "AB-Negative"
    },
    {
        "question": " Holly Golightly is a character in which film?",
        "answers": [
            "Breakfast at Tiffanys",
            "Pretty In Pink",
            "Funny Face",
            "Singing In The Rain"
        ],
        "answer": "Breakfast at Tiffanys"
    },
    {
        "question": " In The Wizard of Oz, the Tin Man wanted to see the Wizard about getting\u2026",
        "answers": [
            "A brain",
            "An oil can",
            "A dog",
            "A heart"
        ],
        "answer": "A heart"
    },
    {
        "question": " Which U.S. state is known as the sunflower state?",
        "answers": [
            "Florida",
            "California",
            "Maine",
            "Kansas"
        ],
        "answer": "Kansas"
    },
    {
        "question": " Which one of these characters isn\u2019t a part of the Friends group?",
        "answers": [
            "Rachel",
            "Joey",
            "Gunther",
            "Monica"
        ],
        "answer": "Gunther"
    },
    {
        "question": " How many bones are there in the human body?",
        "answers": [
            "206",
            "205",
            "201",
            "209"
        ],
        "answer": "206"
    },
    {
        "question": " Which famous singer released a song called \u201cAdore You\u201d?",
        "answers": [
            "Harry Styles",
            "Dua Lipa",
            "Halsey",
            "Shawn Mendes"
        ],
        "answer": "Harry Styles"
    },
    {
        "question": " Fe is the chemical symbol for\u2026",
        "answers": [
            "Zinc",
            "Hydrogen",
            "Fluorine",
            "Iron"
        ],
        "answer": "Iron"
    },
    {
        "question": " How old do you have to be to enter the hunger games?",
        "answers": [
            "12",
            "11",
            "10",
            "15"
        ],
        "answer": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": " What language is the most spoken worldwide?",
        "answers": [
            "Chinese",
            "Spanish",
            "Arabic",
            "English"
        ],
        "answer": "Chinese"
    },
    {
        "question": " What year did Barbie come out?",
        "answers": [
            "1958",
            "1959",
            "1956",
            "1961"
        ],
        "answer": "1959"
    },
    {
        "question": " What is Shakespeare\u2019s shortest tragedy?",
        "answers": [
            "Macbeth",
            "Hamlet",
            "Romeo & Juliet",
            "Othello"
        ],
        "answer": "Macbeth"
    },
    {
        "question": " What is the #1 cookie in the U.S.?",
        "answers": [
            "Chips Ahoy!",
            "Milano",
            "Girl Scout Thin Mints",
            "Oreo"
        ],
        "answer": "Oreo"
    },
    {
        "question": " How many hearts does an octopus have?",
        "answers": [
            "1",
            "2",
            "3",
            "4"
        ],
        "answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": " Who wrote The Scarlett Letter?",
        "answers": [
            "Shakespeare",
            "Stephen King",
            "Nathanial Hawthorne",
            "Ernest Hemingway"
        ],
        "answer": "Nathanial Hawthorne"
    },
    {
        "question": " Which social media platform came out in 2003?",
        "answers": [
            "Myspace",
            "Twitter",
            "Facebook",
            "Tumblr"
        ],
        "answer": "Myspace"
    },
    {
        "question": " Which planet in our solar system is the largest?",
        "answers": [
            "Jupiter",
            "Saturn",
            "Neptune",
            "Earth"
        ],
        "answer": "Jupiter"
    },
    {
        "question": " The Powerpuff Girls are 3 distinct colors. What are they?",
        "answers": [
            "Red, yellow, green",
            "Yellow, blue, green",
            "Blue, green, red",
            "Green, purple, orange"
        ],
        "answer": "Blue, green, red"
    },
    {
        "question": " Which boyband sings the song \u201cI Want It That Way\u201d?",
        "answers": [
            "One Direction",
            "Backstreet Boys",
            "NSYNC",
            "New Kids On The Block"
        ],
        "answer": "Backstreet Boys"
    },
    {
        "question": " Who painted the Sistine Chapel ceiling?",
        "answers": [
            "Picasso",
            "Da Vinci",
            "Michelangelo",
            "Van Gogh"
        ],
        "answer": "Michelangelo"
    },
    {
        "question": " In which state did the Salem Witch Trials take place?",
        "answers": [
            "Washington",
            "Virginia",
            "Massachusetts",
            "Pennsylvania"
        ],
        "answer": "Massachusetts"
    },
    {
        "question": " Which ocean is the largest?",
        "answers": [
            "Indian",
            "Pacific",
            "Atlantic",
            "Arctic"
        ],
        "answer": "Pacific"
    },
    {
        "question": " Which New York City building is the tallest:",
        "answers": [
            "Empire State Building",
            "Bank of America Tower",
            "One World Trade Center",
            "Statue of Liberty"
        ],
        "answer": "World Trade Center"
    },
    {
        "question": " What does the \u201cE\u201d in Chuck E. Cheese stand for?",
        "answers": [
            "Ernest",
            "Edward",
            "Entertainment",
            "Extra"
        ],
        "answer": "Entertainment"
    },
    {
        "question": " Which country gifted the Statue of Liberty to the U.S.?",
        "answers": [
            "Germany",
            "China",
            "France",
            "Italy"
        ],
        "answer": "France"
    },
    {
        "question": " Who painted the Mona Lisa?",
        "answers": [
            "Van Gogh",
            "Da Vinci",
            "Picasso",
            "Monet"
        ],
        "answer": "Da Vinci"
    },
    {
        "question": " In which city were Anne Frank and her family in hiding?",
        "answers": [
            "Paris",
            "Amsterdam",
            "Brussels",
            "Frankfurt"
        ],
        "answer": "Amsterdam"
    },
    {
        "question": " There are 4 best friends on the TV show Pretty Little Liars: Hanna, Emily, Aria, and\u2026",
        "answers": [
            "Mona",
            "Charlie",
            "Alison",
            "Spencer"
        ],
        "answer": "Spencer"
    },
    {
        "question": " In which decade does the Netflix series Stranger Things take place?",
        "answers": [
            "The \u201870s",
            "The \u201880s",
            "The \u201890s",
            "The early 2000s"
        ],
        "answer": "The \u201980s"
    },
    {
        "question": " Which country consumes the most chocolate?",
        "answers": [
            "Spain",
            "Germany",
            "North America",
            "Switzerland"
        ],
        "answer": "Switzerland"
    },
    {
        "question": " What is Sodium Chloride?",
        "answers": [
            "Salt",
            "Sugar",
            "Chlorine",
            "Bleach"
        ],
        "answer": "Salt"
    },
    {
        "question": " Which astrological sign is a crab?",
        "answers": [
            "Pisces",
            "Aquarius",
            "Cancer",
            "Virgo"
        ],
        "answer": "Cancer"
    },
    {
        "question": " In the Bible, how does the Virgin Mary learn of her pregnancy with baby Jesus?",
        "answers": [
            "God tells her",
            "The angel Gabriel tells her",
            "She has a dream about it",
            "A doctor tells her"
        ],
        "answer": "The angel Gabriel tells her"
    },
    {
        "question": " Who, in the Harry Potter series, is Tom Riddle?",
        "answers": [
            "A student in Harry\u2019s class",
            "A professor at Hogwarts",
            "Harry\u2019s birth father",
            "Voldemort"
        ],
        "answer": "Voldemort"
    },
    {
        "question": " The movie The Social Network is about which social media platform:",
        "answers": [
            "Facebook",
            "Myspace",
            "Instagram",
            "Twitter"
        ],
        "answer": "Facebook"
    },
    {
        "question": " Who wrote the songs for The Lion King? ",
        "answers": [
            "Elton John",
            "Phil Collins",
            "Celine Dion",
            "Stevie Wonder"
        ],
        "answer": "Elton John"
    },
    {
        "question": " How many daughters does Barack Obama have?",
        "answers": [
            "0",
            "1",
            "2",
            "3"
        ],
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": " Which Disney princess sings \u201cJust Around The Riverbend\u201d?",
        "answers": [
            "Snow White",
            "Pocahontas",
            "Elsa",
            "Belle"
        ],
        "answer": "Pocahontas"
    },
    {
        "question": " Which biblical narrative is connected to Palm Sunday?",
        "answers": [
            "Jesus\u2019 entry into Jerusalem",
            "Jesus\u2019 resurrection",
            "Jesus feeding the thousands",
            "Nothing, it just means to go to church on Sunday/the day of rest"
        ],
        "answer": "Jesus\u2019 entry into Jerusalem"
    },
    {
        "question": " In Harry Potter and the Sorcerer\u2019s Stone, who gives Harry the invisibility cloak?",
        "answers": [
            "Ron",
            "Snape",
            "Dumbledore",
            "No one; he just finds it"
        ],
        "answer": "Dumbledore"
    },
    {
        "question": " How many boroughs are there in New York City?",
        "answers": [
            "4",
            "5",
            "6",
            "10"
        ],
        "answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": " In the U.S. version of The Office, Michael Scott burns his foot on:",
        "answers": [
            "Hot water",
            "Pavement/cement",
            "Rocks on fire",
            "A George Foreman Grill"
        ],
        "answer": "George Foreman Grill"
    },
    {
        "question": " The superstition believes that when the groundhog sees his shadow, it means:",
        "answers": [
            "Early spring",
            "6 more weeks of winter",
            "It\u2019s going to rain",
            "A tornado is coming"
        ],
        "answer": "6 more weeks of winter"
    },
    {
        "question": " What is the longest river in the world?",
        "answers": [
            "Amazon",
            "Congo",
            "Nile",
            "Hudson"
        ],
        "answer": "Nile River"
    },
    {
        "question": " How many days are in February during a leap year?",
        "answers": [
            "28",
            "29",
            "30",
            "31"
        ],
        "answer": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": " How many degrees are in a circle?",
        "answers": [
            "360",
            "180",
            "150",
            "359"
        ],
        "answer": "360 degrees"
    },
    {
        "question": " Which city is known as the City of Love?",
        "answers": [
            "Rome",
            "Barcelona",
            "New York City",
            "Paris"
        ],
        "answer": "Paris"
    },
    {
        "question": " As an adult, how many teeth should you have in your mouth?",
        "answers": [
            "35",
            "32",
            "30",
            "42"
        ],
        "answer": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": " What was the name of the boy who won Willy Wonka\u2019s factory?",
        "answers": [
            "Charlie Baxter",
            "Charlie Brown",
            "Charlie Bones",
            "Charlie Bucket"
        ],
        "answer": "Charlie Bucket"
    },
    {
        "question": " Edward Scissorhands is known for cutting:",
        "answers": [
            "Hair",
            "Bushes",
            "Clothes",
            "Everything"
        ],
        "answer": "Everything"
    },
    {
        "question": " In which city would you find the Fisherman\u2019s Bastion?",
        "answers": [
            "Rome",
            "Budapest",
            "Barcelona",
            "Athens"
        ],
        "answer": "Budapest"
    },
    {
        "question": " Which U.S. president doesn\u2019t/didn\u2019t have a dog in the White House?",
        "answers": [
            "Trump",
            "Obama",
            "Bush",
            "Lincoln"
        ],
        "answer": "Trump"
    },
    {
        "question": " What does the \u201cU\u201d stand for in \u201cUFO\u201d?",
        "answers": [
            "Unidentified",
            "Under",
            "United",
            "Unique"
        ],
        "answer": "Unidentified"
    },
    {
        "question": " Which U.S. state is known as \u201cAmerica\u2019s Dairyland\u201d?",
        "answers": [
            "Minnesota",
            "Iowa",
            "Pennsylvania",
            "Wisconsin"
        ],
        "answer": "Wisconsin"
    },
    {
        "question": " Usher found a young boy singing on YouTube and made him into a famous singer. What\u2019s that kid\u2019s name?",
        "answers": [
            "Niall Horan",
            "Jaden Smith",
            "Shawn Mendes",
            "Justin Bieber"
        ],
        "answer": "Justin Bieber"
    },
    {
        "question": " Which Olympic sport is Michael Phelps known for?",
        "answers": [
            "Snowboarding",
            "Skiing",
            "Running",
            "Swimming"
        ],
        "answer": "Swimming"
    },
    {
        "question": " What is the complementary color of green?",
        "answers": [
            "Blue",
            "Yellow",
            "Red",
            "Purple"
        ],
        "answer": "Red"
    },
    {
        "question": " Han Solo is a character from which movie series:",
        "answers": [
            "Harry Potter",
            "Star Wars",
            "Lord of the Rings",
            "Indiana Jones"
        ],
        "answer": "Star Wars"
    },
    {
        "question": " In Men and Black, what are the two FBI agents hunting?",
        "answers": [
            "Serial killers",
            "Ghosts",
            "Aliens",
            "Time travelers"
        ],
        "answer": "Aliens"
    },
    {
        "question": " The most recent seasons of American Idol have the judges Katy Perry, Lionel Richie, and\u2026",
        "answers": [
            "Trace Adkins",
            "Luke Bryan",
            "Blake Shelton",
            "Keith Urban"
        ],
        "answer": "Luke Bryan"
    },
    {
        "question": " How many Harry Potter books are there?",
        "answers": [
            "7",
            "8",
            "6",
            "10"
        ],
        "answer": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": " What breed of dog is the most popular in the U.S.?",
        "answers": [
            "Pug",
            "Dalmatian",
            "Beagle",
            "Golden Retriever"
        ],
        "answer": "Golden Retriever"
    },
    {
        "question": " Which rapper was known for his album Blue Slide Park?",
        "answers": [
            "J Cole",
            "Post Malone",
            "Eminem",
            "Mac Miller"
        ],
        "answer": "Mac Miller"
    },
    {
        "question": " How many sides does a hexagon have?",
        "answers": [
            "5",
            "6",
            "7",
            "8"
        ],
        "answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": " In which city was Ferris Bueller\u2019s Day Off filmed?",
        "answers": [
            "Pittsburgh",
            "Chicago",
            "NYC",
            "San Francisco"
        ],
        "answer": "Chicago"
    },
    {
        "question": " The UK is made up of the following countries: England, Ireland, Wales, and\u2026",
        "answers": [
            "France",
            "Hungary",
            "Scotland",
            "Austria"
        ],
        "answer": "Scotland"
    },
    {
        "question": " How many elements are there on the periodic table?",
        "answers": [
            "112",
            "118",
            "120",
            "143"
        ],
        "answer": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": " Where is the United Nations Headquarters?",
        "answers": [
            "D.C.",
            "NYC",
            "Philadelphia",
            "Orlando"
        ],
        "answer": "NYC"
    },
    {
        "question": " What famous singer sings with Taylor Swift in her song \u201cMe!\u201d?",
        "answers": [
            "Brendan Urie",
            "Shawn Mendes",
            "Ellie Goulding",
            "Halsey"
        ],
        "answer": "Brendan Urie"
    },
    {
        "question": " In what year did women get the right to vote?",
        "answers": [
            "1910",
            "1920",
            "1930",
            "1940"
        ],
        "answer": "1920"
    },
    {
        "question": " Where in the United States is the largest aquarium?",
        "answers": [
            "New Jersey",
            "Maine",
            "California",
            "Georgia"
        ],
        "answer": "Georgia"
    },
    {
        "question": " There are 5 great lakes in the United States: Lake Michigan, Lake Superior, Lake Ontario, Lake Erie, and\u2026",
        "answers": [
            "Lake Huron",
            "Lake Hartwell",
            "Lake Tahoe",
            "Great Bear Lake"
        ],
        "answer": "Lake Huron"
    },
    {
        "question": " Neil Armstrong was the first man\u2026",
        "answers": [
            "On Mars",
            "On a spacecraft alone",
            "On the Moon",
            "To travel to the sun"
        ],
        "answer": "On the Moon"
    },
    {
        "question": " What does \u201cFBI\u201d stand for?",
        "answers": [
            "Female Body Inspector",
            "Federal Bureau of Investigation",
            "Federal Business of Investigation",
            "Federal Bureau of Inspection"
        ],
        "answer": "Federal Bureau of Investigation"
    },
    {
        "question": " What is the deadliest snake?",
        "answers": [
            "Python",
            "Cobra",
            "Cobra",
            "Black Mamba"
        ],
        "answer": "Black Mamba"
    },
    {
        "question": " In The Office, what object of Dwight\u2019s does Jim put in jello?",
        "answers": [
            "Computer mouse",
            "Wallet",
            "Stapler",
            "Coffee mug"
        ],
        "answer": "Stapler"
    },
    {
        "question": " In Friends, how many times has Ross been married?",
        "answers": [
            "Only once",
            "3 times",
            "Twice",
            "More than 3 times"
        ],
        "answer": "3 times"
    },
    {
        "question": " What is a group of lions called?",
        "answers": [
            "Squad",
            "Pack",
            "Herd",
            "Pride"
        ],
        "answer": "Pride"
    },
    {
        "question": " How many keys are on a piano?",
        "answers": [
            "86",
            "87",
            "88",
            "89"
        ],
        "answer": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": " What was the name of the Greek mythological woman who had snakes for hair?",
        "answers": [
            "Pandora",
            "Helen",
            "Cassiopeia",
            "Medusa"
        ],
        "answer": "Medusa"
    },
    {
        "question": " What do you call a baby goat?",
        "answers": [
            "Kid",
            "Goatee",
            "Child",
            "Baby Goat"
        ],
        "answer": "Kid"
    },
    {
        "question": " According to Phineas and Ferb, there are __ days of summer vacation?",
        "answers": [
            "90",
            "103",
            "104",
            "110"
        ],
        "answer": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": " What is the most populous city in Canada?",
        "answers": [
            "Toronto",
            "Ontario",
            "Quebec",
            "Vancouver"
        ],
        "answer": "Toronto"
    },
    {
        "question": " The Da Vinci Code opens with a murder in which museum:",
        "answers": [
            "The Guggenheim",
            "The Louvre",
            "The Van Gogh museum",
            "The Metropolitan Museum of Art"
        ],
        "answer": "The Louvre"
    },
    {
        "question": " From which TV show is the family of Roses: Johnny, Moira, David, and Alexis?",
        "answers": [
            "Bob\u2019s Burgers",
            "Schitt\u2019s Creek",
            "Parenthood",
            "7th Heaven "
        ],
        "answer": "Schitt\u2019s Creek "
    },
    {
        "question": " After The Simpsons, what is the longest-running TV show?",
        "answers": [
            "Law & Order",
            "Grey\u2019s Anatomy",
            "Criminal Minds",
            "NCIS"
        ],
        "answer": "Law & Order"
    },
    {
        "question": " Which Disney princess sings \u201cA Dream Is A Wish Your Heart Makes\u201d?",
        "answers": [
            "Belle",
            "Cinderella",
            "Jasmine",
            "Sleeping Beauty"
        ],
        "answer": "Cinderella"
    },
    {
        "question": " How often does the moon orbit the Earth?",
        "answers": [
            "Every 7 days",
            "Every 27 days",
            "Every 30 days",
            "Every 365 days"
        ],
        "answer": "Every 27 days"
    },
    {
        "question": " In Greek Mythology, who is the Queen of the Underworld?",
        "answers": [
            "Pandora",
            "Medusa",
            "Helen",
            "Persephone"
        ],
        "answer": "Persephone"
    },
    {
        "question": " How many points are a touchdown worth?",
        "answers": [
            "5",
            "6",
            "7",
            "8"
        ],
        "answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": " How many feet are in a mile?",
        "answers": [
            "1,037",
            "5,288",
            "5,280",
            "6,201"
        ],
        "answer": "5,280 feet"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the Oval Office located in the White House?",
        "answers": [
            "North Wing",
            "South Wing",
            "East Wing",
            "West Wing"
        ],
        "answer": "West Wing"
    },
    {
        "question": " At what temperature (Fahrenheit) does water freeze?",
        "answers": [
            "32 degrees",
            "40 degrees",
            "-10 degrees",
            "0 degrees"
        ],
        "answer": "32 degrees"
    },
    {
        "question": " Where in Pennsylvania is The Office based?",
        "answers": [
            "Philadelphia",
            "Pittsburgh",
            "Scranton",
            "Lancaster"
        ],
        "answer": "Scranton"
    },
    {
        "question": " In the movie Good Will Hunting, which college does Skylar attend?",
        "answers": [
            "Harvard",
            "Yale",
            "Columbia",
            "UCLA"
        ],
        "answer": "Harvard"
    },
    {
        "question": " Where in California is Disneyland located?",
        "answers": [
            "Malibu",
            "Huntington Beach",
            "Los Angeles",
            "Anaheim"
        ],
        "answer": "Anaheim"
    },
    {
        "question": " \u201cI see dead people\u201d is a line from which horror film\u2026",
        "answers": [
            "The Sixth Sense",
            "The Grudge",
            "The Shining",
            "The Exorcist "
        ],
        "answer": "The Sixth Sense"
    },
    {
        "question": " Who founded Microsoft?",
        "answers": [
            "Bill Hader",
            "Steve Jobs",
            "Bill Gates",
            "Mark Zuckerberg"
        ],
        "answer": "Bill Gates"
    },
    {
        "question": " In which city was the movie National Treasure filmed?",
        "answers": [
            "Washington D.C.",
            "NYC",
            "Philadelphia",
            "Roanoke"
        ],
        "answer": "Philadelphia"
    },
    {
        "question": " Which classic novel has the line \u201cStay Gold, Ponyboy\u201d?",
        "answers": [
            "The Catcher in the Rye",
            "1984",
            "The Outsiders",
            "Catch-22"
        ],
        "answer": "The Outsiders"
    },
    {
        "question": " What was the name of Harry Potter\u2019s pet owl?",
        "answers": [
            "Hedwig",
            "Luna",
            "Dobby",
            "Fluffy"
        ],
        "answer": "Hedwig"
    },
    {
        "question": " Which Disney princess had 3 fairy godmothers?",
        "answers": [
            "Cinderella",
            "Snow White",
            "Sleeping Beauty",
            "Jasmine"
        ],
        "answer": "Sleeping Beauty"
    },
    {
        "question": " Which band came back together in 2019?",
        "answers": [
            "The Naked Brothers Band",
            "The Jonas Brothers",
            "One Direction",
            "The Beatles"
        ],
        "answer": "The Jonas Brothers"
    },
    {
        "question": " Steve Jobs is known for wearing a black\u2026",
        "answers": [
            "Button-down shirt",
            "T-shirt",
            "Turtleneck",
            "Blazer"
        ],
        "answer": "Turtleneck"
    },
    {
        "question": " In which movie does Anne Hathaway play a poor, homeless woman?",
        "answers": [
            "The Devil Wears Prada",
            "Les Miserables",
            "The Princess Diaries",
            "Ella Enchanted "
        ],
        "answer": "Les Miserables"
    },
    {
        "question": " The movie 10 Things I Hate About You was based on which play by Shakespeare:",
        "answers": [
            "Taming of the Shrew",
            "Hamlet",
            "Romeo and Juliet",
            "A Midsummer Night\u2019s Dream"
        ],
        "answer": "The Taming of the Shrew"
    },
    {
        "question": " Where does Nathan\u2019s Hot Dog Eating Contest take place?",
        "answers": [
            "Coney Island",
            "Miami Beach",
            "Mall of America",
            "Orlando"
        ],
        "answer": "Coney Island"
    },
    {
        "question": " What age did Amy Winehouse, Janis Joplin, and Jimi Hendrix die?",
        "answers": [
            "26",
            "27",
            "29",
            "30"
        ],
        "answer": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": " Which two planets in our solar system are known as \u201cice giants\u201d?",
        "answers": [
            "Neptune and Jupiter",
            "Uranus and Pluto",
            "Pluto and Jupiter",
            "Neptune and Uranus"
        ],
        "answer": "Neptune + Uranus"
    },
    {
        "question": " What country is Prague in?",
        "answers": [
            "Hungary",
            "Austria",
            "Czech Republic",
            "Germany"
        ],
        "answer": "Czech Republic"
    },
    {
        "question": " What is the actress\u2019s name in Funny Face, Sabrina, and Roman Holiday?",
        "answers": [
            "Audrey Hepburn",
            "Natalie Wood",
            "Marilyn Monroe",
            "Grace Kelly"
        ],
        "answer": "Audrey Hepburn"
    },
    {
        "question": " Which poet wrote the poem \u201cThe Raven\u201d? ",
        "answers": [
            "Robert Frost",
            "Edgar Allen Poe",
            "Walt Whitman",
            "Sylvia Plath"
        ],
        "answer": "Edgar Allen Poe"
    },
    {
        "question": " How many ribs are in the human body?",
        "answers": [
            "16",
            "24",
            "19",
            "29"
        ],
        "answer": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": " Who was the 16th president of the United States?",
        "answers": [
            "Lincoln",
            "Nixon",
            "Jackson",
            "Madison"
        ],
        "answer": "Lincoln"
    },
    {
        "question": " Who wrote the novel Slaughterhouse-Five?",
        "answers": [
            "Kurt Vonnegut",
            "Stephen King",
            "J.D. Salinger",
            "Harper Lee"
        ],
        "answer": "Kurt Vonnegut"
    },
    {
        "question": " In The Office, what was the food that Dwight grew on his farm?",
        "answers": [
            "Pumpkins",
            "Beets",
            "Onions",
            "Potatoes"
        ],
        "answer": "Beets"
    },
    {
        "question": " What animal is associated with ancient Egypt?",
        "answers": [
            "Lion",
            "Cat",
            "Hummingbird",
            "Rabbit"
        ],
        "answer": "Cat"
    },
    {
        "question": " In 2016, a musician won the Nobel Peace Prize for Literature. Who was it?",
        "answers": [
            "Lenny Kravitz",
            "Eric Clapton",
            "Bob Dylan",
            "Elton John"
        ],
        "answer": "Bob Dylan"
    },
    {
        "question": " How many time zones are there in the world?",
        "answers": [
            "7",
            "24",
            "23",
            "9"
        ],
        "answer": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": " What was the movie\u2019s name that featured Matthew McConaughey, Michael Caine, Anne Hathaway, John Lithgow, and Matt Damon?",
        "answers": [
            "Flight Plan",
            "The Martian ",
            "Interstellar",
            "Ad Astra"
        ],
        "answer": "Interstellar"
    },
    {
        "question": " How many rings are there in the Olympic symbol?",
        "answers": [
            "5",
            "7",
            "4",
            "9"
        ],
        "answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": " Twilight was both a book and a movie, with the main character Bella Swan being pulled into two different love directions with Edward Cullen and\u2026",
        "answers": [
            "Jasper Hale",
            "Jacob Black",
            "Billy Black",
            "Dr. Cullen"
        ],
        "answer": "Jacob Black"
    },
    {
        "question": " What is celebrated on December 26th?",
        "answers": [
            "The day after Christmas",
            "Harvest Day",
            "Boxing Day",
            "National Dog Day"
        ],
        "answer": "Boxing Day"
    },
    {
        "question": " What is the name of the second American astronaut to step foot on the moon?",
        "answers": [
            "Buzz Aldrin",
            "Neil Armstrong",
            "Alan Bean",
            "James Irwin"
        ],
        "answer": "Buzz Aldrin"
    },
    {
        "question": " How many eyes does a spider have?",
        "answers": [
            "8",
            "9",
            "10",
            "2"
        ],
        "answer": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": " What is the first book of the Old Testament in the Bible?",
        "answers": [
            "Matthew",
            "Proverbs",
            "Genesis",
            "Exodus"
        ],
        "answer": "Genesis"
    },
    {
        "question": " Which founding father is known for his large handwriting on the Declaration of Independence?",
        "answers": [
            "John Hancock",
            "Thomas Jefferson",
            "John Adams",
            "Alexander Hamilton"
        ],
        "answer": "John Hancock"
    },
    {
        "question": " What was the first Disney film that was produced in color?",
        "answers": [
            "Cinderella",
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs",
            "Sleeping Beauty",
            "Pocahontas"
        ],
        "answer": "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs"
    },
    {
        "question": " Sodium bicarbonate is used in the kitchen as what?",
        "answers": [
            "Salt",
            "Sugar",
            "Baking soda",
            "Vinegar"
        ],
        "answer": "Baking soda"
    },
    {
        "question": " In the 1983 movie National Lampoon\u2019s Vacation, what is the name of the fictional amusement park the Griswold family is trying to go to?",
        "answers": [
            "Dorney Park",
            "Walley World",
            "Six Flags",
            "Dollywood"
        ],
        "answer": "Walley World"
    },
    {
        "question": " In Ray Bradbury\u2019s novel Fahrenheit 451, what are they burning?",
        "answers": [
            "Clothes",
            "Houses",
            "Books",
            "Money"
        ],
        "answer": "Books"
    },
    {
        "question": " What was the first capital of the United States?",
        "answers": [
            "Washington, D.C.",
            "Richmond",
            "Boston",
            "Philadelphia"
        ],
        "answer": "Philadelphia"
    },
    {
        "question": " Which actor performs music under the stage name Childish Gambino?",
        "answers": [
            "Donald Glover",
            "Will Smith",
            "Frank Ocean",
            "Tyler, The Creator"
        ],
        "answer": "Donald Glover"
    },
    {
        "question": " Which water sport is the official sport for the state of Hawaii?",
        "answers": [
            "Water polo",
            "Swimming",
            "Water skiing",
            "Surfing"
        ],
        "answer": "Surfing"
    },
    {
        "question": " In the movie The Princess Bride, what is Westley\u2019s response to Buttercup\u2019s requests?",
        "answers": [
            "\u201cOkay.\u201d",
            "\u201cOf course, I love you.\u201d",
            "\u201cAs you wish.\u201d",
            "\u201cAnything for you.\u201d"
        ],
        "answer": "\u201cAs you wish.\u201d"
    },
    {
        "question": " What is the name of the company that published the Mario Kart video game?",
        "answers": [
            "Nintendo",
            "Electronic Arts (EA)",
            "SEGA",
            "Xbox"
        ],
        "answer": "Nintendo"
    }
]